visiblebody.com 2016-06-23

# Visible Body | 3D Human Anatomy | Privacy Policy

This Website is owned and maintained by Argosy Publishing, Inc. ("Company", "we," or "us"). Company can be contacted by mail at Attn: Information, 109 Oak Street, Suite 203, Newton Upper Falls, MA 02464, or by e-mail at [info@argosypublishing.com](mailto:info@argosypublishing.com). The following policies apply to www.visiblebody.com and all other Websites owned and operated by Company.

1\. Collection of Personal Information from Site Visitors  
For all visitors, Company may automatically collect and/or track the following information: (1) home server domain name; (2) information provided by visitors in online forms (including email) and surveys; and (3) aggregate/user-specific information on how many times certain pages are accessed and what Web pages and application functions visitors use. A cookie may be placed on your machine to enable Company to collect the aggregate/user-specific information listed above. In addition, Company may collect certain statistical information about users' visits, such as how many people visit our site, the users' IP addressees, which pages users visit on our site, from which domains users reach our site, and which browsers they use. We use these statistics about user visits for aggregation purposes only, to help us improve the usefulness of the site.

2\. Use of Personal Data Collected  
Personal data collected by Company will be used by Company for editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of users' behavior, for product development, for content improvement, to inform advertisers as to how many visitors have seen or clicked on their advertisements, and to customize content and layout of Company's site. Data on visitors' home servers is aggregated for internal review and then discarded. Names, postal and e-mail addresses, and phone numbers collected may be added to Company's databases and used for future communications regarding site updates, new products and services, and upcoming events.

3\. Disclosure of Personal Data to Third Parties  
Company may, at its option, share, rent, sell or otherwise disclose personal data (other than credit card numbers) to third parties whom Company has pre-screened, and who market products and/or services that Company determines, in its sole discretion, might be of interest to visitors of Company's Website.

We may also share personal information collected as described above with other individuals and organizations who need to have access to such information in connection with our marketing and promotional efforts and who have agreed to maintain the confidentiality of such information. For example, when you sign up for our email newsletter, your email address and other information you provide will be transmitted to our third-party marketing vendor, who will retain that information for sending you our email newsletter.

Certain purchases by you of Company products may be conducted by an online authorized reseller using its own Website, accessed through Company's Website. In such cases, the personal information you provide to the authorized reseller in connection with the purchase will be subject to the authorized reseller's own privacy policy. The reseller may in turn share with Company personal data about you in connection with these transactions. Company will use this information in compliance with its own Privacy Policy.

We also reserve the right to release information as required by any governmental or law enforcement agency or under a court order issued by a court of competent jurisdiction.

4\. Collection of Personal Data from Children  
Company does not attempt to collect personal information from children under age 13. Personal information sent to Company, such as e-mail, which appears to be from a child, is deleted. Company cannot always determine if a visitor to its Website or the sender of an e-mail is a child.

5\. Company's Right to Contact User  
Company reserves the right to contact site visitors regarding changes to the Website Terms and Conditions, Privacy Policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to the Website.

6\. Links  
This Website contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage visitors to be aware when they leave our site, and to read the privacy policies of each and every Website that collects personal information. Except as otherwise provided herein, this privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website.

7\. Security  
While we have instituted security measures to protect the information and systems that we maintain, we cannot guarantee that all transmissions to and from our Websites are secure. E-mails that you send to us may be subject to interception. If your communication includes personal information that you do not wish to provide electronically, please contact us by postal mail or telephone.

8\. Company's Right to Change Privacy Policy  
Company reserves the right to change this policy at any time, without notice, by posting the new or revised privacy policy at this location: [http://www.visiblebody.com/privacy.](http://www.visiblebody.com/privacy)
